all right so the last computer that you
need that I'm recommending is some sort
of tower that has a lot of
ram so that you can chop it up into
virtual machines and have up to 50 60 70
little tiny Linux machines on there um
this is an Opti uh also an HP it's
refurbished it's it's under you know
$800 uh again so that's the third of the
computer the first two the first one is
the laptop the second one is a Mini
Server if you will to get your feet wet
with how to do a server and the third is
an actual tower that you can practice
chopping up into different Linux virtual
machines and reconfiguring on the Fly
and and that's pretty much it if you
have that everything else is just an
addition you probably want to get
network stuff but I don't know if I'll
talk about that those are the three main
things that I would budget for in your
home lab